Finding Aid for the Benjamin Aaron Papers LSC.0413
UCLA Library Special Collections
Benjamin Aaron papers
circa 1930-2006
1970-2000
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0413
36.8 Linear Feet (32 boxes and 24 cartons)
UCLA Professor of Law Emeritus Benjamin Aaron's principal field of study was labor law and industrial relations with a special emphasis on comparative labor law. Materials include arbitration case files, conference files, documents pertaining to Aaron's involvement in the National Academy of Arbitrators, the Industrial Relations Research Association, and the International Society of Labor Law and Social Security, correspondence, UAW Public Review Board documents, publications authored by and collected by Aaron, drafts of Aaron's memoirs, and files concerning the UCLA Ad Hoc Committee chaired by Aaron to examine three allegations against Acting Assistant Professor of Philosophy, Angela Y. Davis.
Restrictions on Access
Portions of this collection are restricted. Consult finding aid for additional information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed digital materials. Digital materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Benjamin Aaron donated to UCLA University Archives, November, 1994. University Archivist Charlotte Brown received additions in November, 2007.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9971895243606533
Biography/History
Benjamin Aaron was born on September 2, 1915 in Chicago, Illinois. He graduated from the University of Michigan in 1937, and received his law degree from Harvard in 1940. In 1946 Aaron joined UCLA's Institute of Industrial Relations, and became its director in 1960. That same year, he joined the faculty of the UCLA School of Law. Aaron was a distinguished scholar of labor law and published widely in the field. He served on many panels, boards, and commissions as an appointee of Presidents Truman, Eisenhower, Kennedy, Johnson, and George H.W. Bush, such as The National Commission on Technology, Automation, and Economic Progress. During his career he served as president of National Academy of Arbitrators, the Industrial Relations Research Association, and the International Society of Labor Law and Social Security. He became Professor of Law Emeritus in 1986. Aaron died August 25, 2007 in Los Angeles, California.
Scope and Content
Collection contains documents pertaining to the career of Benjamin Aaron, a scholar of labor law and law school professor at UCLA. Materials include arbitration case files, conference files, documents pertaining to Aaron's involvement in the National Academy of Arbitrators, the Industrial Relations Research Association, and the International Society of Labor Law and Social Security, correspondence, UAW Public Review Board documents, publications (both authored by and collected by Aaron), drafts of Aaron's memoirs, and files concerning the UCLA Ad Hoc Committee chaired by Aaron to examine three allegations against Acting Assistant Professor of Philosophy, Angela Y. Davis.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection maintains the creator's original order and file names.
University of California, Los Angeles. School of Law--Faculty -- Archives
- Law School Admissions Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Law School Admissions Committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Content
  Correspondence and flyers concerning UCLA Law Student demonstrations and strike against a fifty percent reduction in Chicano enrollment.
- Statewide Academic Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Statewide Academic Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Academic Senate, Los Angeles Division (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Correspondence concerning academic freedom and the "Jensen Incident" involving the cancellation of Professor Jensen's lecture.
- Correspondence - IIR - U of C, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- FMCS Arbitration Service Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Comparative Labor law Conference, 1967 Nov 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Strikes and Lockouts - Working Papers (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary labor law Arbitration - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary labor law Arbitration - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary labor law Arbitration - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary labor law Arbitration - An Analytical Comparison - Proposal (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary labor law Arbitration - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary Labor Arbitration - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Courts and American Voluntary Labor Arbitration: An Analytical Comparison (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Strikes and Lockouts - Outlines, Notes, Memoranda (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Strikes and Lockouts Correspondence, Notes, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Strikes and Lockouts Correspondence, Notes, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Strikes and Lockouts Correspondence, Notes, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - European Labor Law Project; Strikes and Lockouts - Admin File (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Comparative Labor Law Group (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Administrative File, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Correspondence, Notes, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Memoranda (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Assembly Advisory Council on Public Employee Relations, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Assembly Advisory Council on Public Employee Relations, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Assembly Advisory Council on Public Employee Relations, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Joint Committee on Public Employer - Employee Relations Personal File (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Memoranda (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Correspondence, Notes, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Correspondence, Notes, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Correspondence, Notes, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Correspondence, Notes (Box 5, Folder 5)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Legistlation, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1982 Jul-Sep (Box 7, Folder 5)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1982 Jul-Sep (Box 7, Folder 6)
- ISLLSS - IXth International Congress, Munich, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1982 Jan-Mar (Box 8, Folder 1)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1982 Apr-Jun (Box 8, Folder 2)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- ISLLSS Executive Committee Meeting in Izmir, 1987 Sep. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- ISLLSS XIIIth World Congress - Athens, 1991 Sep (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Third European Regional Congress on Labor Law and Social Security - Paris, 1989 Sep 13-15 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- IIRA European Congress - Vienna (Box 10, Folder 4)
- International Encyclopedia of Comparative Law: Labor law - Labor Courts and Grievance Arbitration Systems, 1968-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- International Encyclopedia of Comparative Law: Labor law - Labor Courts and Grievance Arbitration Systems, 1968-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- International Encyclopedia of Comparative Law: Labor law - Labor Courts and Grievance Arbitration Systems - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- International Encyclopedia of Comparative Law: Labor Law - Labor Courts and Grievance Arbitration Systems - Memoranda, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- USIS. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- African Trip Lectures. - Photos, News Clippings, Vistas and Travel Tickets, 1973 Sep 23-Oct 27 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- African Trip Lectures: Zambia, South Africa, Ethiopia, 1973 Sep 23-Oct 27 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Lectures - Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Lectures - Trieste., 1973 Jul 22-27 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Lectures - AMP. - Swansea Whales, 1973 Jul 9-13 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Lectures - Paris., 1973 Apr 2-4 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Lectures - Cyprus., 1973 Mar 12-17 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Lectures - Salzburg. Seminar in American Studies: The Social Impact of the New Technology Session #110, 1967 Jun 16-Jul 7 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Lectures - Salzburg. Seminar in American Studies: The Social Impact of the New Technology Session #110, 1967 Jun 16-Jul 7 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Salzburg Seminar - Lecture Notes and Materials (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Comparative Labor Law - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Comparative Labor Law - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Comparative Labor Law - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- IIRA - Third World Congress, London, Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector, 1973 Sep (Box 13, Folder 3)
- IIRA - Third World Congress, London, Multinational Enterprises, 1973 Sep (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Workshop on Labor Law, London School of Economics, 1967 Jul 10-14 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- CCH Second Annual Labor and Employment Law Symposium, Arlington, VA, 1988 Nov 17 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- CCH Labor and Employment Law Symposium, 1987 Oct 16 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Phi Beta Kappa Lectures (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Phi Beta Kappa Visiting Scholar Program, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Material for Phi Beta Kappa Lectures (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Phi Beta Kappa Visiting Scholar Program, Wofford College, 1979 Apr 30-May 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Phi Beta Kappa Visiting Scholar Program, Coe College, 1979 Apr 26-27 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Phi Beta Kappa Visiting Scholar Program, Illinois College, 1979 Mar 5-6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- UCLA Institute of Industrial Relations Faculty Advisory Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- UCLA Institute of Industrial Relations Ad Hoc Review Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- UCLA Institute of Industrial Relations, 1975 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- IRR-GBA (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - IRR - U of C, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Center for the Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- FMCS Arbitration Services Advisory Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- FMCS Arbitration Services Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Lectures - University of Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1984 August (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
- Industrial Relations Law Journal (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Editorial Board, Labor History, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
- Fifth National Convention of the Industrial Relations Society of Australia, 1986 Sep 26-28 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Arbetslivscentrum, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Arbetslivscentrum - Comparative Labor Law Research - National Reports (Box 16, Folder 6)
- California Rural Legal Assistance (Box 16, Folder 7)
- LA County Employee Relations Ordinance (Box 17, Folder 1)
- LA County Employee Relations Ordinance (Box 17, Folder 2)
- LA County Employee Relations Ordinance (Box 17, Folder 3)
- UTLA and City of Los Angeles Board of Education - Mediation Diary (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Western Airlines and ALPA, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles County Employee Relations Commission Ad Hoc Panel - General File (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles County Employee Relations Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- LA County Employee Relations Ordinance (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles County Employee Relations Commission, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
- Employee Relations Ordinance for Los Angeles County - Report and Recommendations of the Consultants' Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1973 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1972 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
- Correspondence, 1972 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1975 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1974 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1974 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1973 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1973 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1976 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1975 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1976 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Comparative Labor Law Group - Discrimination in Employment - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1977 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1977 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1977 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1981 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1980 Jan 1-Dec 31 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1979 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1979 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1978 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1978 Jan 1-Dec 31 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1985 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1985 Jan 1- Jun 30 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1984 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1984 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1983 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1983 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1982 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1982 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1981 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1987 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1987 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1986 Jul 1-Dec 31 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1986 Jan 1-Jun 30 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Labor Law Group, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Labor Law Group, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Labor Law Group, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Labor Law Group, 1970 Jan-May (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Labor Law Group, 1970 Jun-Dec (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Labor Law Group, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Labor Law Group, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
- Econ Dept, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Nat'l League of Cities/U.S. Conference of Mayors (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Arb. Trans World Airlines and ALPA - Route Swapping Grievance, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
- Arb. Trans World Airlines and ALPA - Post Award Interpretations, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Arb. Trans World Airlines and ALPA (Route Swap Grievance), 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Arb. Trans World Airlines and ALPA Master File, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
- Trans International Airlines and ALPA - ALPA Exhibits (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Trans International Airlines and ALPA - TIA Exhibits (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Speeches, Reprints, Book Reviews (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
- P.G.E. v. Confederated Tribes of Warm Springs - Expert Testimony, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Fifty Years of Labor Law and Social Security: Main Developments and Prospects, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 5-6)
- Case Western University Law School - Symposium on Arbitration, 1988 Oct 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- National War Labor Board: Grievance Arbitration Tapes, 1988 Oct 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- IIR 20th Anniversary: 20 Years of Changing Labor Attitudes, 1987 Jun 24 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- The Future of Interest Arbitration in the Public and Private Sectors, 1986 Jan 7 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Air Transport Labor Relations Conference, 1987 Jun 17-18 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Government Controls of Union Elections, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Angela Davis - Ad Hoc Committee - Report to C. Young, circa 1970 Mar (Box 32, Folder 1)
  General note
  Ad Hoc Committee Report to Chancellor Charles E. Young concerning its examination of three allegations against Acting Assistant Professor of Philosophy, Angela Y. Davis. This report is signed by Chairman Benjamin Aaron and the following professors: Walter R. Goldschmidt, Wendell P. Jones, Ada B. Nisbet, Charles R. Nixon, Lynn White and Robert M. Yost. Materials also include the American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Statement on Professional Ethics and Statement on Academic Freedom.
- Angela Davis - Public Speeches, 1969 Oct-1970 Feb (Box 32, Folder 2)
  Materials include transcripts of Davis' speeches at Campbell Hall, Pauley Pavillion, Berkeley's Lower Plaza and the Thirteenth Annual People's World Banquet.
- Angela Davis - Lecture Notes, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
  Copies of six lectures from Fall Quarter.
- Angela Davis - Department of Philosophy Materials, 1969 Jan-1970 Mar (Box 32, Folder 5)
  Correspondence to Department of Philosophy Chairman Donald Kalish and Philosophy Professor David Kaplan concerning Davis' qualifications as an educator.
- Angela Davis - AAUP Materials, 1963-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  Copies of AAUP Bulletins concerning academic freedom and tenure.
- Angela Davis - Course Evaluation Sheets, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  Copies of course evaluations for Davis' Philosophy 99, Philosophy 107 and Philosophy 180.
- Angela Davis - Correspondence, 1970 Jun-Sep (Box 32, Folder 8)
  Letters concerning Davis' dismissal, Communist Party membership and the Angela Davis Fund.
- Angela Davis - Academic Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  Materials include University of California, Los Angeles Division of the Academic Senate Resolutions and Minutes concerning the Angela Davis Case, the UCLA Department of Philosophy's Statement of Facts Concerning the Appointment and Threatened Dismissal of Professor Angela Davis, press releases issued by Angela Y. Davis and Associate Professor of Philosophy, David Kaplan, a leaflet from the Committee for an Orderly University, a statement from the UCLA Committee of Concerned Faculty which includes a calendar of events in the case and the Angela Davis Defense Committee's Policy Statement concerning the Regents' dismissal of Davis.
- Angela Davis - Ad Hoc Committee, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  Materials include correspondence from Chairman Aaron to members of the Ad-Hoc Committee, a statement to the Regents regarding the reappointment of Davis, a letter from Chancellor Charles Young to the Ad-Hoc Committee and clippings.
- Angela Davis - AAUP Draft Report, 1971 May 12 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  A copy of the AAUP Draft Report concerning the Davis case and correspondence concerning revisions.
- Angela Davis - Correspondence and Minutes, 1969-1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, Committee on Academic Freedom Minutes and Committee on Educational Policy Minutes concerning the Angela Davis Case.
- Relevant Court Cases: Under Railway Labor Act (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Stanford University: Grievance Procedure for Non-academic Employees (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Stanford University: Faculty Discipline Cases, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- University of California, Berkeley: Termination Grievances at the Cowell Memorial Hospital Psychiatric Clinic, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Firestone Tire and Rubber Company and Locals 10726-United Rubber Workers (Los Angeles and Salinas plants) -- general file, 1967-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- United Airline Pilots' System Board of Adjustment (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Reform of the Representation Process in American Labor Law, 1982 Jul-Sep (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Special Project [Directory of Law Libraries] (Box 33, Folder 8)
- United States District Court case files (Box 33, Folder 9)
- NAA: Proposed Modification of Provision in Code of Professional Responsibility Against Advertising (Box 33, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA) Tribunal Appeals Comm., 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- NAA Comprehensive Strategic Plan: Strategies for the Future, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- NAA, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- NAA, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- NAA, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- NAA, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- NAA, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- NAA, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- NAA, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- NAA Annual Meetings 1st-3rd June 2000 San Francisco, 2000 Jun (Box 33, Folder 20)
- NAA, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- NAA, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- NAA, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- UAW Public Review Board Decision Nos. 1400-1480 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Aaron Publications and Speeches (Box 34, Folder 2)
- University of Hawaii Conference on "Challenges to Collective Bargaining", 1967 Aug 11 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Amnesty International (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Bureau of Employment Security Seminar: The Effects of Automation and Technological Change, 1967 Mar 30 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- 11th Annual Research Conference on Industrial Relations, 1968 Mar 11 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Arbitration case records, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Arbetslivscentrum correspondence and seminar speeches, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Australia and New Zealand (Box 35, Folder 1)
- The College of Labor and Employment Lawyers (Box 35, Folder 2)
- NAA and NDC Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 4)
- United Auto Workers (UAW) Public Review Board (Box 35, Folder 5)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 7)
- ILO Interview, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- ILO Convention No. 105 Forced Labor (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Arbitration Decisions C-D "Notebook" (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Arbitration Decisions A-B (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Comparative Labor Laws & Policy Journal (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Continental Airlines and ALPA Mediation File, Nov 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- UCLA School of Law, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Labor and the Anti-trust Laws Encyclopedia of the American Constitution, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Institute of Industrial Relations 40th Anniversary Conference, 1986 Oct 17-18 (Box 36, Folder 2)